Daniel Brown

BLOCKCHAIN DEVELOPER

ABOUT ME

Experienced software engineer with a passion for quality code and good design. Skilled in Solidity with emphasis on NFTs, smart contract auditing and DApps. Well versed and familiar with tools like Truffle, Remix, Hardhat, Jest and various others. Always excited about exploring new languages and tools. Committed to life-long learning.



1 (870) 818- 6803



danbrown501@gmail.com https://github.com/DanBrown501/BlockChain



SKILLSET

Truffle

Javascript

React

Solidity

ethers.is

Hardhat

Public Speaking

Leadership

Written Communication

Native English Speaker

Unit Testing

Integration Testing

Team/Community Builder

Can Play the G Chord On Any Guitar

EDUCATION

2020 - 2021

SPRINGBOARD Software Engineer Track

EXPERIENCE

AUGUST 2021 - CURRENT

GASPOS, INC Full Stack Developer - C#, Azure, PowerBuilder

- · Developed high performance and reusable software with excellent test coverage
- · Integrated with existing corporate and partner applications which span multiple languages and frameworks
- Evaluated existing and new technologies and ensured applications utilize industry best practices

MAY 2018 - AUGUST 2021

ARKANSAS DREAM CENTER, INC Community Coordinator - Leadership

- Team Lead. This included hiring, performance reviews and training employees.
- Liaison between high level donors and the Dream Center.
- Pioneered mentorship programs, recruited volunteers and procured resources through donations.